<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.rt.hightec.dave.feature"
      label="HighTec DAvE Importer Feature"
      version="1.2.0.3938-201107110904"
      provider-name="HighTec EDV-Systeme GmbH">

   <description url="http://www.hightec-rt.com">
      [Enter Feature Description here.]
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.hightec-rt.com">
      [Enter Copyright Description here.]
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.hightec-rt.com">
      
 END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT 
 
 IMPORTANT - READ CAREFULLY 
 
 This HighTec EDV-Systeme GmbH (hereinafter referred to 
 as &quot;HighTec&quot;) End User License Agreement (hereinafter also 
 referred to as &quot;EULA&quot;) is a legal agreement between an 
 individual person or a legal entity (hereinafter referred to as 
 &quot;Customer&quot;) and HighTec on the use of computer software 
 and accessories developed and supplied by HighTec 
 (hereinafter referred to as &quot;Software&quot;). By installing or using 
 or registering to use the Software, Customer agrees to be 
 bound by the provisions set down in this agreement. If 
 Customer does not agree to these terms, he is not permitted to 
 use the software. 
 
 HighTec and their suppliers are the owners of any intellectual 
 property rights in the software supplied hereunder. HighTec 
 permits Customer to download, install, use and otherwise 
 benefit from the software in strict accordance with the 
 provisions of this agreement. The use of third-party software, 
 materials and services such as GNU or GPL-based software 
 included in or accessed in connection with the software might 
 be subject to the Terms and Conditions of the respective third 
 parties. The third-party software, materials and services are 
 displayed in the information screen of the respective Software 
 or identified by HighTec on request of Customer at any time. 
 
 The Software is fitted with product activation procedures 
 (license manager) designed to prevent unauthorised copying. 
 Any attempt to circumvent the restrictions on unauthorised 
 copying shall result in the immediate termination of this 
 agreement and loss of any rights of use on the part of 
 Customer. In such a case, further use of the licensed software 
 is liable to copyright infringement and further legal claims. 
 
 1 Licensing procedure 
 
 The Software is licensed, not sold, to the Customer. In 
 accepting this agreement, Customer acknowledges that the 
 Software remains the sole property of HighTec and/or their 
 licensors. Nothing contained in this agreement will be 
 construed as granting any ownership to Customer. 
 
 When obtaining the Software, the Customer receives a license 
 key that is interpreted by the License Manager included in the 
 Software. This procedure simplifies the installation process, 
 and allows the Customer to have the acquired licenses 
 available immediately after the purchase of the respective 
 license. 
 
 Customer has the choice between several license types 
 according to his requirements. The license types are handled 
 by a License Manager, which determines where a user can 
 install and use the Software, and how many copies of the 
 Software can be active at any given time. The License 
 Manager supports evaluation as well as networked and single 
 licenses. 
 
 2 License types 
 
 The following license types are available: 
 
 2.1 Node-locked 
 This is the most basic license type. It is granted for either a 
 fixed or an unlimited number of licenses. The licenses are tied 
 to the host-IDs of the computers where the Software is 
 installed and used. A Node-locked License can have a version 
 number, an expiration date, and other specific attributes. This 
 license information is protected by means of digital 
 signatures. 
 
 2.2 Temporary (Short Term) Licenses 
 This license restricts the use of the Software to a predefined 
 period of time. It is especially interesting for customers who 
 wish to realise a short-term project after which they do no 
 longer need the software. 
 
 2.3 Floating 
 Due to its not being tied to specific host-IDs, this license 
 allows the use of the Software anywhere on the network, as 
 long as the maximum number of purchased licenses is not 
 exceeded. The License Server handles the license grants via 
 the network. 
 
 2.4 Time-zone-based 
 This license restricts the use of the Software to one or more 
 time zones, thus offering a favourable solution for 
 multinational enterprises that do not require world-wide 
 licenses since they intend to use the Software only in certain 
 regions. 
 
 2.5 Roaming 
 With this license type, users running licensed applications on 
 their company network can disconnect from the network and 
 take their licenses with them for working from home or in the 
 field. Licenses that are thus &quot;checked out&quot; expire after a 
 predetermined number of days or weeks, or can be returned to 
 the license pool at the company network. Should the roaming 
 user need an extension while he is away from the company 
 network, all he needs to do is temporarily reconnect to the 
 network in order to refresh the roaming period. 
 
 2.6 Evaluation 
 This license is tied to a special Evaluation host-ID and can be 
 used on any computer. It is, however, furnished with an 
 expiry date. 
 
 2.7 Shared 
 This license allows multiple copies of the same executable to 
 be used under just one license. This is an important feature for 
 the use of compilers and/or debuggers. 
 
 2.8 Host-ID lists 
 This is mainly used in connection with single licenses. The 
 license can be tied to several host-IDs set down in a list 
 instead of to a single host-ID. This method makes it possible 
 for the user to install and use the Software, for example, at his 
 office desktop and at his laptop. 
 
 3 Terms of License 
 
 Upon payment of the applicable license fees, HighTec hereby 
 grants to Customer the non-exclusive, non-transferable right 
 to:
 
 a) use the Software, solely for the design, simulation, 
 implementation and manufacture of User Products 
 (Developing License); 
 b) In case the Customer is developing own products by the 
 means of or running under runtime environments or parts 
 thereof, e.g. runtime libraries, of HighTec, e.g. PXROS or 
 PXROS-HR, a runtime license for each manufactured 
 processor or controller may be demanded for such product 
 (Distribution License). Such Distribution License may be 
 granted 
 a) as license per product (payable annually or 
 quarterly); 
 b) against flat-fee payment for a definite time for a 
 certain product or product line and independent from the 
 number of items; or 
 c) unlimited in time or number of items 
 against payment of a lump-sum (&quot;Buy-out&quot;).
 
 3.1 Customer is permitted to make one backup copy of the 
 Software for archiving purposes, which may only be installed 
 in cases where the original copy of the Software is lost, 
 corrupted or made unavailable in any way other than by use 
 or possession by another person. 
 
 3.2 If Customer has purchased more than a single license, 
 then this EULA allows the simultaneous use of the Software 
 by several persons employed by Customer or hired as 
 contractors (provided that such contractors oblige themselves 
 in writing to observe the confidentiality obligations as per 6. 
 of this Agreement). In doing so, the number of persons 
 having access to and/or using the Software may not exceed 
 the overall number of purchased licenses at any time. 
 Customer understands and agrees that any use beyond the 
 licensed number shall constitute not only breach of this 
 EULA, but also a violation of national and international 
 copyright and patent laws. 
 
 4 Further Restrictions on Use, Disclosure; 
 Third-Party License Rights 
 
 4.1 License, Not Sale. The Software is licensed, not sold, to 
 Customer. In no event shall Customer be permitted to sell, 
 license or otherwise commercialise the Software as standalone 
 products. 
 
 4.2 Source Code Availability 
 Parts of the Software (the HighTec compiler toolchain in 
 particular) are GPL-based software. For these parts, the 
 source code can be delivered to the Customer on request 
 against a handling fee. This offer is valid for a period of three 
 years after the official release of the HighTec compiler 
 toolchain. 
 
 4.3 No Assignment or Sharing. In no event shall Customer 
 disclose, transfer, assign, publish, distribute, rent, lease or in 
 any other way make Software available to third parties 
 without the prior written consent by HighTec. 
 
 4.4 No Reverse Engineering. Customer understands and 
 agrees that in no event shall he make unauthorized copies of, 
 decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, modify, or 
 otherwise reduce the Software or any portion thereof to a 
 form perceivable by a human reader, or disclose to any third 
 person any portion of the Software in such a form. The right 
 to decompile the Licensed Product granted to Customer is 
 only granted under the terms of sec. 69 e para. (1) nos. 1 to 3 
 UrhG and within the limits of sec. 69 e para. (2) nos. 1 to 3 
 UrhG. 
 
 4.5 Restrictions on Disclosure. Customer may not provide, 
 disclose or in any other way make available to others, 
 including but not limited to Customer's affiliates, subsidiaries 
 or divisions (unless Customer has licensed the Software in a 
 way that permits such use) or any third parties, any of the 
 Software without the prior written permission of HighTec. In 
 the event that Customer hires or engages any contractor for 
 the purpose of assistance with the installation, implementation 
 or other use of the Software, Customer shall first establish the 
 fact that said contractor is not employed or engaged by any 
 direct competitor of HighTec, and in the event such contractor 
 is so employed or engaged, Customer shall in no event give 
 such person access to the Software; in the event such 
 contractor is not employed or engaged by a direct competitor 
 of HighTec, Customer shall ensure that such contractor has 
 signed before obtaining access to the Software an appropriate 
 confidentiality declaration that protects the Software in a 
 manner consistent with the confidentiality and other 
 provisions in this EULA. 
 
 4.6 Third-Party Licenses. The rights granted in the scope of 
 this agreement only relate to Software developed by HighTec. 
 Customer understands and agrees, that the Software may 
 contain software and/or other intellectual property rights 
 owned by third parties and that it is not HighTec's obligation 
 or responsibility to determine what, if any, third party licenses 
 Customer has to obtain in connection with the third party 
 software, in case Customer should decide to exploit the 
 Software beyond the scope of the License granted to him by 
 HighTec and Customer agrees to indemnify, defend and hold 
 harmless HighTec and HighTec's officers, directors, 
 employees, subsidiaries, affiliates and distributors from any 
 liability, including but not limited to attorneys' fees and 
 experts' fees associated in any way with Customer's failure to 
 obtain or properly maintain any such required third party 
 licenses. 
 
 4.7 Limit on Applications. The Software is no consumer 
 product and is designed to be used by trained professionals 
 for professional purposes exclusively. Due to the large variety 
 of applications for the Software, it has not been tested in all 
 situations where it might be used. HighTec shall not be liable 
 in any way for the results obtained by Customer through use 
 of the Software. Customer agrees that he is responsible for 
 any decisions regarding the use or way of use of the Software 
 and for the results thereof. Customer agrees to indemnify, 
 defend and hold harmless HighTec and its officers, directors, 
 employees and agents from any third-party claims arising out 
 of decisions by Customer to use or test the Software and out 
 of any results from such use or testing by Customer. 
 
 4.8 Compliance Certification. During the term of this 
 Agreement, HighTec shall have the right to request that 
 Customer provides within thirty (30) days after receipt of 
 HighTec's written request, documentation and certification of 
 the use of the Software in complete compliance with this 
 EULA's terms and conditions. 
 
 5 Intellectual Property Rights 
 
 Customer acknowledges that all Intellectual Property Rights 
 in the Software are and will remain the sole property of 
 HighTec or its licensors, if any. Nothing contained in this 
 EULA will be construed as transferring by implication, 
 estoppel or otherwise any ownership, license or other rights to 
 Customer except the licenses and rights expressly granted 
 hereunder. 
 
 6 Confidentiality 
 
 Customer acknowledges and agrees that the Software and all 
 other information provided by HighTec under this EULA are 
 to be kept in confidence, and not to be disclosed except as 
 permitted by this EULA. Customer acknowledges and agrees 
 that the Software constitutes the trade secrets and proprietary 
 information of HighTec and/or third parties. Customer agrees 
 that he shall only make the Software available to his 
 employees or to consultants/independent contractors who 
 have entered into a confidentiality agreement with Customer 
 in a sufficient way to protect HighTec's intellectual property 
 rights in the Software. Customer undertakes to use sufficient 
 safeguards to protect the Software from unauthorised access 
 by third parties. 
 
 7 Online Services 
 
 7.1 Online Services Availability and Use. The Software 
 may rely upon or facilitate Customer's access to websites 
 maintained by HighTec or other parties offering goods or 
 services (&quot;Online Services&quot; herein). Customer's access to and 
 use of any such website, or of any such Online Services, is 
 completely governed by the terms, conditions and disclaimers 
 existing on such websites, or in connection with such Online 
 Services. HighTec may at any time, at their discretion, 
 eliminate, alter or modify the availability of any such website 
 or any such Online Services. 
 
 7.2 No Connection with Third Party Online Service 
 Providers. HighTec does not control, endorse or accept any 
 responsibility or liability in connection with websites or 
 Online Services provided by third parties, even if HighTec 
 includes references or links to such websites on their own 
 website. Any communications or other dealings between 
 Customer and any third party in connection with access to or 
 use of any such website or Online Services, including, but not 
 limited to, delivery and payment terms, are solely between 
 Customer and such third party. In no event shall HighTec be 
 liable to Customer for any failures, deficiencies or errors in 
 complying with applicable laws by such third party website or 
 Online Service providers. 
 
 7.3 Internet Based License Management System. In the 
 event that Customer has licensed the Software from HighTec 
 on an on-demand basis, such that access is effected via the 
 Internet Based License Management System, Customer 
 understands and agrees that nothing herein shall constitute a 
 guarantee or warranty for such Internet Based License 
 Management System to be available to Customer at any and 
 all times. 
 
 
 8 Taking effect; termination 
 
 This EULA is valid from the date of being signed by both 
 parties or the date of the installation or use of the Software on 
 an computer or within an environment of Customer, whatever 
 will occur first, and will remain effective either: (a) for the 
 period of time for which Customer has licensed the Software, 
 or (b) until terminated by either party. Customer may 
 terminate this EULA at any time by destroying the Software 
 and all copies thereof. This EULA will terminate immediately 
 without notice from HighTec if Customer breaches any 
 provision of this EULA. Any payment obligations accruing 
 prior to such termination shall survive and remain due. Upon 
 termination of this EULA, the licenses and rights granted 
 hereunder and the obligations imposed hereunder will cease, 
 and Customer shall destroy the Software including all copies 
 and all relevant documentation. The provisions of all sections 
 which by their nature would survive the termination of this 
 EULA shall so survive and Customer shall be obligated to 
 perform in accordance therewith. 
 
 9 Limited Remedy and Disclaimer 
 
 HighTec warrants for a period of twelve (12) months from the 
 Effective Date of the applicable HighTec Product License 
 Sales Order Form that the unmodified and in case of an online 
 delivery error free transmitted Software obtained thereunder 
 and paid by Customer will perform in substantial 
 conformance with the technical specifications set forth in the 
 Documentation; provided, however, that HighTec makes no 
 warranty with respect to any such failure or incorrect result 
 that may arise due to: (i) the quality of the data sought to be 
 processed with the Software; (ii) the effects of other software 
 not licensed by HighTec to Customer or developed by 
 HighTec for Customer; or (iii) the use of the Software in an 
 operating environment or on a platform not specified by 
 HighTec. Unless otherwise explicitly agreed upon, HighTec 
 does not provide any warranty for third parties software, e.g. 
 software components being subject of the GNU General 
 Public License. HighTec does not assume any responsibility 
 for any defects, damages or consequential damages which 
 may occur in connection with the use of an illegal or not fully 
 paid copy of the software. 
 
 HighTec warrants the CD-ROMs, DVD's, diskettes or other 
 media on which the Software is provided to Customer to be 
 free of defects in materials and workmanship under normal 
 use for thirty (30) days after delivery. 
 
 THE WARRANTIES ABOVE ARE EXCLUSIVE AND IN 
 LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, WHETHER 
 EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED 
 WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS 
 FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. 
 
 HighTec does not warrant that the Products will meet 
 Customer's requirements, that the Products will operate in the 
 combinations which Customer may select for use, that the 
 operation of the Products will be uninterrupted or error-free 
 or that all Product errors will be corrected. To the extent 
 Customer obtains any pre-production releases of Products, 
 such Products are distributed &quot;as is&quot; with no warranty of any 
 kind. 
 
 10 Exclusive Remedies 
 
 For any breach of the warranties contained in this Section, 
 Customer's exclusive remedy, and HighTec's entire liability, 
 shall be: 
 
 -For Software: At HighTec's sole discretion, the 
 correction of Software errors that cause breach of the 
 warranty, replacement of such Software. In case 
 HighTec should not be willing or able to cure software 
 errors, Customer may at his sole discretion demand 
 reduction or return of the fees paid to HighTec for the 
 license of such Software.
 
 -For Media: The replacement of defective media 
 returned within thirty (30) days after delivery. 
 
 11 Limitation of Liability 
 
 In no event shall either party be liable for any indirect, 
 incidental, special or consequential damages, or damages for 
 loss of profits, revenue, data or use, incurred by either party 
 or any third party, whether in an action in contract or tort, 
 even if the other party has been advised of the possibility of 
 such damages. HighTec's liability for damages hereunder 
 shall in no event exceed the double amount of fees paid by 
 Customer under this Agreement, and if such damages result 
 from Customer's use of the Product or services, such liability 
 shall be limited to double the amount of fees paid for the 
 relevant Product or services giving rise to the liability from 
 the Effective Date of the applicable HighTec Product License 
 Sales Order Form or the date of performance of the applicable 
 services. This does not apply, if the damages were caused by 
 HighTec gross negligently or intentionally.The provisions of 
 the Agreement between the Parties allocate the risks between 
 HighTec and Customer. HighTec's pricing reflects this 
 allocation of risk and the limitation of liability specified 
 herein. 
 
 12 Non-Assignment 
 
 Except as stated otherwise, neither this EULA, nor any 
 interest herein or part hereof, are assignable or transferable 
 without HighTec's prior written consent, including any 
 transfer or assignment by operation of law, agreement of 
 merger, sale of assets or otherwise. 
 
 13 Governing Law, Venue 
 
 This EULA shall be governed by the laws of Germany, 
 without reference to conflict of law or choice of law 
 principles or decisions. The parties agree on Saarbruecken, 
 Germany, as the exclusive place of jurisdiction. HighTec is 
 entitled to sue the Customer at every other admissible venue. 
 
 14 Severability Clause 
 
 Should one or multiple provision(s) of this agreement be or 
 become ineffective, this shall not affect the validity of the 
 remaining provisions. In such a case, the ineffective 
 provision(s) shall be replaced by such that is/are as similar as 
 possible as regards content, and which comes closest to the 
 ineffective or unfeasible provision(s) regarding its/their 
 purpose. The same applies to possible loopholes in this 
 agreement. 
 
 15 Entire Agreement 
 
 This agreement and HighTec's Standard Terms and 
 Conditions for the Sale and Lease of Goods represent the 
 complete and exclusive understanding between the parties 
 and supersede all prior agreements, understandings and 
 communications related to the subject matter of this 
 agreement, be they oral or in writing. No addition or 
 modification to this EULA is valid unless made in writing 
 and signed by authorised personnel of HighTec and the 
 Customer. 

   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.6.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.core" version="5.2.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime.compatibility" version="3.2.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.managedbuilder.core" version="7.0.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="com.rt.hightec.framework.common" version="1.2.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="com.rt.hightec.framework.buildsystem" version="1.2.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.rt.hightec.dave.importer"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.0.3938-201107110904"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
